This is a $250 million private island.
Literally anything you could ever want is on this private island.
And I'm going to show you the difference between this and a $150 million luxury island.
A massive $45 million island.
A $5 million frozen island all the way down to the world's cheapest private island.
That thing.
I'm starting to realize we might not all fit on it.
First step on my brand new island.
Here's your dollar.
Thank you sir.
Thank you for selling it to me.
It's yours now buddy.
Let's check out what I just bought.
My first impression is a lot smaller than I thought.
When you pay a dollar you get a random pile of bricks.
An old toilet.
I found the restroom.
And a bunch of random wooden poles.
There's more poles than square feet on this thing.
They're actually called pylons.
Let's pile onto that boat and leave.
And as you can see there's nothing here.
So I'm going to blow it up.
Well later in this video we're going to a $150 million island.
And also a quarter billion dollar super island.
But first we're going to head over to the one million dollar island called Monkey Island.
Yes you heard me right.
This island is literally swarmed with hundreds of monkeys.
I can see why it's called Monkey Island.
What's this monkey?
It's Odie.
Odie took my orange.
Okay.
Monkey sleep with monkey take.
All the monkeys on this island have a strategy for interacting with people.
They gaslight you into thinking that you're friends.
And then they steal your food.
You can have it.
There's a monkey on the boat.
And if you're wondering where you and your friends are going to sleep on this island.
Suspended above the water are six luxury cabanas.
Which house both humans and monkeys.
The monkey's grabbing the GoPro Jimmy.
Sir, we need this for filming.
I just need to borrow this.
Thank you.
Okay.
I got my camera back.
You want it?
Oh.
He wants your hat.
Okay.
You can have that sir.
By the end of this I'm going to be naked.
The monkeys are stealing everything.
And the monkeys are not even the coolest part of this island.
See, this island isn't even an island at all.
It's actually on top of a massive underwater plant network that emerged from the sand and
water to create this illusion of an island that we see today.
Is this a million dollar island or a million dollar bush because there's no land?
What do you think?
I don't know.
I think an island is what you make of it.
And on the other side of the island there's even a private relaxation area and a beach
front massage parlor.
I'm trying not to fall in the water.
I'm about to get a massage with a monkey.
That's really cool.
Notice how all the water around here is freezing.
What?
That took a lot of effort.
And we put that much effort in to convey that the five million dollar island is very
cool.
And where we're going next most of the year looks like this.
But it's going to look like this.
No joke this island is so cold right now that the lake around it is actually frozen
solid.
Which means to get there we're going to be using an interesting vehicle.
We're literally hovering.
Yeah, apparently snowmobiles are just too basic for this island.
It just had to be hovercrafts.
This is awesome.
I'm about to arrive in a fashion.
And it only took about 30 seconds of being outside the hovercraft for the gang to be
frozen solid.
How cold is it?
It's zero degrees Celsius.
Pretty cold man.
Even more like a 70 guy.
And so they hurried over to these futuristic self heated huts to stay warm.
Oh this is so small.
Wait, there's no room for you in here.
We're going to check out a little bit.
And these huts are able to stay here completely year round.
Because not only can they float on warm peaceful lake water, but they also do just fine in the
dead of winter.
But at least in the winter you get a great view of the northern lights.
For five million dollars you basically get a winter wonderland.
And while staying on this island you're given unlimited five star food.
I think he thinks we should finish.
And even though this island comes with a luxury cabin to stay in.
Oh this is beautiful.
Fine, I'll take it.
Jimmy buy it for me.
They ended up spending most their time on the frozen lake where they were able to ride
an actual dog sled.
I took your glove.
This is the best island.
I don't know how any island is going to beat this.
Maybe one where I could feel my hands.
And Carl's hands are in luck because the next island is not only warm, but more expensive
than all of the other islands combined.
This island is tiny, but arguably one of the most luxurious ones out there.
Okay let's go check out the house.
Wow.
Oh wow.
We're stoked to have you as our guests.
We hope you have a blast.
Just don't break anything.
Yo we should try to break one thing.
Ooh nice bathroom.
Usually rich people like showers that can fit like thirty to a thousand people in them.
This time they chose a reasonable shower.
When you pay sixteen million dollars in addition to a shower that's the size of the one
dollar island.
The private island comes with this helicopter that's apparently too big for the island.
We have jet skis, we have a submarine, another submarine to the right.
We have a shark submarine over there.
There's almost a submarine for each of us.
Boys do whatever you want.
Have fun.
Oh no really bad.
It's a little private island.
This is gonna walk my car to be to get off of this thing.
Whoa we're under a fish now.
And after Ludwig and Carl kiss the sea at five hundred miles per hour.
We went back to shore to take a little breather.
Yeah Ludwig's gonna jump out of a helicopter.
He really is.
No I'm not.
Eddie last word.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
This helicopter is taking the boys up into the air and letting them jump and free fall into the ocean.
Oh my god.
This is crazy.
We shouldn't be doing this.
This is only a sixteen million dollar island and we're jumping out of helicopters.
He's about to jump.
Oh my god.
Oh wait they jump.
There it goes.
Whoever said money doesn't buy happiness doesn't own that private island.
Because I'm pretty happy.
And now the forty five million dollar island.
This island is so big you can't even fit it all in frame.
Oh hey.
I didn't even realize they were waiting on us.
I always feel uncomfortable when I pull up the places and people are just standing
potentially for hours waiting on me.
Hello.
We have some blueberry smoothies here.
Is it alcoholic?
No it is not.
He's not twenty one.
Now we'll take you guys up and we'll show you around where I live in a little bit.
Let's see what forty five million dollars gets us.
It's a long path.
The path is longer than the lost island.
For forty five million dollars this island comes with a mansion
and its own beachside bar and private chef.
Can I give it a flip?
Sure.
Nothing bad.
And outside of the mansion is a hot tub overlooking the cove where the jet skis are.
And of course a pool with the best view I've ever seen.
Does this look as cool on camera as it does in real life?
And if for some reason you don't want to stay in the mansion
there's five luxury beachside cabanas you can pick from.
Jimmy.
May I?
You may.
I have class.
But even after messing around with all of the amenities
Why are we playing ping pong when we have an entire island?
It's important to note that that's not what makes this island special.
All the way on the other end of the island are sentry old ruins that we are yet to explore.
Tips on driving.
Oh no.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
We're going to go on-roading a little bit and head to the back of the island now.
How does Carl always end up driving?
Because I'm also a big bum.
Dude this is like a safari.
Yeah you're going four times the speed limit.
I mean I don't know if there's cops that will stop you but I'm just letting you know.
Is there a jail in this island?
No jail.
Oh there's no jail?
And when we finally ran out of road to drive on
we started to make our way through what used to be a village of people in this island
over a hundred years ago.
This used to be a bar?
Yep.
Yeah you want to walk under this hundred year old giant thousand pound slag?
Sure.
Surely it won't fall on top of you.
Dude if today was the day that it fell you couldn't even be mad.
Nolan come over here before you die.
And just past these ruins is easily the best view on the entire island.
Whoa.
Oh yeah it gets better.
We were driving for so long I forgot we were on an island.
The island starts over there, comes all the way around, wraps all the way around here,
goes down that coastline all the way up over there.
I'll be honest I personally wouldn't pay $45 million for a big jungle with some ancient ruins
but I'm sure some rich guy will.
This next island is arguably the second most expensive island that money can buy.
This is the $150 million island.
It comes with eight luxurious mega mansions and the best part is it's completely powered
by solar panels and wind turbines.
It's home to some of the most exotic animals I've ever seen and took over four decades
to build.
This island will literally blow your mind.
When I think of a private island this is what I think of.
That's good because this is a private island.
All right.
And apparently the first thing you need to do here is watch your trip.
Make sure you don't taint the island with your outside world germs.
I've already washed my germs.
Does everyone who come here gets a coconut?
I mean they're not running low.
True.
I don't know if it's because this place is so fancy or maybe they just heard about
Carl's driving.
But each of us ended up with our own personal driver.
I have a feeling this is going to be a once in a lifetime experience.
How much did you come back?
I might be out of my price range.
And even though this island costs $150 million you can actually rent it for yourself.
For the extremely low price of $140,000 per day.
I didn't even realize we just went up a mountain.
I've heard this is the most luxurious private island in the world.
It is.
The view is insane.
This is the Great House.
But before we were able to explore the Great House my dumb friends got distracted by
a turtle.
There's a turtle?
Get in there.
Yeah!
All right.
You guys go to the rest of the island.
This island is so extra that for every one person in your party
they have ten staff members waiting on your every knee.
There's a bunch of people over there like here's drinks, here's food.
What do you want to do over the next two days?
And we're just like turtle.
Yeah!
And of course Nolan of all my friends wanted to take advantage of this.
What's everyone up to over here?
We're playing pool with ten people.
They're my hype crew.
Now you don't have to hang out with them to make it feel good.
I will be sad if you don't sit down and relax.
Okay.
If you need attention don't make them stand up.
It's only been an hour but I'll say it.
This is the best island so far.
On top of all of that the island has a house with a driving range on the roof where you
can hit golf balls into the ocean because these are made of fish food.
Ooh.
You should probably hit it further so you don't hit someone.
Look at all those flamingos.
There's so much I can't process it.
Wow flamingos in the sky.
They're everywhere.
They don't love us unless we give them food.
Come here my brethren.
But flamingos aren't the only exotic animals on this island.
Whoa.
That's a dinosaur.
This is so cool.
And believe it or not this tortoise could live to be over 200 years old.
Mr. tortoise my name is Jimmy.
If my descendants descendants descendants come here tell them I was awesome.
And afterwards we got sworn by a bunch of lemurs that live on this island.
Get over here.
Jimmy I don't know if you notice that there's two lemurs on here.
Yeah I know.
I'm trying not to move.
I'll put food on there.
Oh please don't.
And if you're wondering where all of these exotic animals came from most of them sadly are endangered
species and are on this island because the owner of Richard Branson brought all of them
here to prevent them from going extinct.
But the most endangered animals on this island were the mermaids that served a sushi.
Mermaids and sushi.
This is luxury.
Mermaids.
Do you guys want sushi?
I would say nice.
Is that cannibalism?
Yeah.
It's like a family reunion.
Get over here.
There's honestly so much on this island we can't even film it all.
We played tennis.
We played basketball.
We explored yet another mansion.
I did my first cold plunge.
You get the idea.
There's so much to do on this island it's actually overwhelming.
This one's actually pretty intense.
I'm like actually scared.
Do you want to know what else is intense?
What?
The final island.
I'll see you there.
Why are we still here?
And on the way to the 250 million dollar island we stopped in shark infested waters
because I have to pay for this video.
And now that I'm surrounded by sharks and what feels like my worst nightmare
I'm going to tell you guys about Stumble Guys.
They're so close.
Oh my gosh.
And the worst part is I'm not coming out until I'm done with this ad.
Stumble Guys is a great to play mobile player game where 32 people compete for the crown.
You have to be an absolute maniac to do this.
Not even Stumble Guys could pay me to do this.
Why are you all here sharks?
Oh.
They're so close.
They're so cool.
And for their new season they went all out with new Mr. B skins, animations, and emotes.
Okay it's going right up.
Bro this is the wall.
I want to make sure there's enough sharks for Jimmy.
They also added a brand new level but you have to follow a pattern as long as possible to stay alive
and the longer you live the harder it gets.
Oh.
The sharks hitting me.
I think the sharks are hitting the cave.
No it's rocking.
Oh this is scary.
I also just released my brand new toolkit.
So you can build your own Mr. B's level.
This is one of their best seasons ever.
You need to try my new Mr. B's level.
Plus build your own and I want to see what you guys come up with.
Oh the sharks keep hitting the caves.
So I'm going to get out of here.
Make sure you download Stumble Guys for free so I don't have to go back to the shark cage.
You're alive.
Let's go do more things that have nothing to do with sharks.
Please.
And now that I've paid off the debt I've incurred from this video
let's visit the $250 million island.
This is a $250 million private island.
This extraordinary island has an entire amusement park with over a dozen waterslides.
It also has its own hot air balloon and just about every activity you could ever imagine.
And we have it all to ourselves.
There are no other guests here.
But out of every feature you've seen on these islands so far
this one stands above the rest.
In the middle of the island is a massive waterslide.
Even though literal eight year olds ride that waterslide
I might still check it out because I'm afraid it hides.
But before taking on the waterslide
we checked out the other features like how there's over a hundred jet skis on this island.
It's a bit overkill.
And not to mention there's a literal zip line that spans across man-made beaches.
What's the helmet for?
What am I going to hit?
The ground, bro.
Because sometimes people fall off.
This is like really scary.
Good luck.
Thank you.
You're kind of far behind.
This is awesome.
This is actually not that crazy.
And if you own this island you can host over 13,000 of your friends
at any of these five gargantuan pools.
Oh.
This kind of looks like it was made in Minecraft.
And it's so funny just seeing my two friends in it.
Nolan looks like a tiny speck.
For $250 million this island of course has exotic animals.
Is that a peacock?
Sir, I need to take you in for questioning.
Sir.
And even every game you can imagine.
I wish there was the 13,000 people that are normally here to watch how bad he is at Cornwall.
Is that soccer pool?
This island has things I didn't even know existed.
But something I noticed is that there were way too many lifeguards at this island for just the four of us.
How many lifeguards are on this island?
Over 100.
Really?
With this many lifeguards you would have to try to drown.
So I thought it would be fun if we gave them all the day off.
Has anyone ever rented this island before?
Wow, this is the first.
Dude, you are leaning back, bro.
You look way too relaxed.
And after all the 100 lifeguards went down,
they decided to hype up me and the boys for our turn to go down the slide.
Boys, you want to know what's even scarier than that?
What?
That one.
Why is it so terrifying?
That looks so scary.
Can we skip it?
Towering at over 135 feet tall.
This is the tallest water slide in all of North America.
I don't even know what I'm looking at.
It's like a skyscraper.
But I'm scared.
Daredevil's Peak.
What a soothing name.
Very inviting.
Oh, we're so high.
It's kind of freaking me out.
All right, we made it to the top.
Are you guys just waiting for us up here?
Yeah.
Listen to how intense the wind is up here.
Oh, don't look down.
Look how crazy the island looks.
Oh my God.
Hey, Carl.
No.
Oh, Nolan.
Would you say Nose Ghost is enforceable?
Nose Ghost is enforceable.
There we go.
Hey, the last part's it.
You got to go, Nolan.
I love you, mom.
I'll see you on the other side.
All right, go.
Oh my God.
I got hit by a truck.
Let's do this.
You better come down after me.
OK.
Oh God.
Why is it so fast?
Is it actually that scary?
I'm going to do this for your entertainment,
giant ride scare me.
Here we go.
That is going so fast.
And even though I was basically just drowning
the entire time down the water slide,
I got to say this whole island was pretty awesome.
Oh yeah, and one more thing.
Make sure you use this QR code to download Stumble Guys,
and you can win $10,000.