I just bought this entire grocery store which includes enough food to literally feed an entire city
and then I decided to trap this random guy inside
and every day you live here I will give you $10,000 in a grocery cart
that's wild dude let's go well I'll give it to you in 24 hours
oh okay this challenge could literally make Alex a multi-millionaire
which in theory means he could be in here for years
and it starts right now all right Jimmy's gone
why would I ever leave I could be here for years time to go grocery shopping baby
now if Alex crosses this red line that we painted around the entire perimeter of the grocery store
the challenge is over and he walks away with his current winnings
and to make sure he stays inside it's worth noting here that we have countless
cameras covering every square inch of the grocery store
for my first meal on night one I guess I'll cook the steak
I think this is just gonna be home base this little corner of the grocery store
if I have meals like this every night I'll easily be here for years
day one complete see you in the morning it has officially been 24 hours and I got the first
10 grand Alex hey do you feel this and confirm it's $10,000
um it is I believe you now we introduce the twist of the challenge
basically to receive the daily $10,000 you need to give me $10,000 in product from the store
and so you have to strategize what order to give rid of these items to stay here as long as possible
oh wow okay conveniently there's a lot of electronics over there that are pretty
expensive for day one that's probably a good idea I can't really eat a tv so it's no use to me
you're 22 cents over all right let me check out do you have nbp card no would you like one no you
want to sign up for here's your cash Chris take it away I will see you tomorrow with another
$10,000 in cash you should start strategizing what you're gonna sell me this changes everything
I gotta start strategizing for the future I have to figure out all the stuff that I need
to get rid of pet food pet items Jimmy cannot pay me to eat this stuff I swear I got $10,000 worth of
dog food right here I think I'm just gonna get some rest wake up early because I'm gonna have to prep
more items tomorrow I got a lot of work ahead of me Alex what's up Jimmy is that what you're
selling to me today it's dog food oh my gosh this is gonna take us forever to move wait can
we do like that I let them clap transition go for it there we go it's all over here at the register
isn't that a cool effect I love beast magic you're at $9,991.80 and for the final item we are now at
$10,045 and something you should know every single item Alex sells to me we are literally gonna
donate to charity so don't worry none of this is gonna go to waste the next few days we're
kind of a breeze for Alex on day five he's so many $10,000 worth of produce all this
produce here they're gonna go bad very fast on day six he sold me a bunch of diapers and on day seven
eight and nine he cleared out an additional $30,000 worth of products he even discovered the back
room of the store and since he hasn't showered in 10 days he built his very own makeshift shower
and laundry system hey how's it going what's up Jimmy all right as of now give me an honest
answer how far do you think you're gonna go oh I mean I feel like a hundred days for sure
oh boy depending on how long Alex lasts this may just become my most expensive video ever but
I'm prepared for that I don't care if you go a year I got the money who put all this in here is
what I wanted the bank you will get this once I get my $10,000 in items all right today I have
more TVs who goes to a grocery store to buy a TV why are these here now Alex to be honest
with me did you empty out any of these TV boxes film with rocks and keep the TV uh dogs
all right I trust him even though that was not what I was asking
approaching day 11 Alex began to get pretty efficient at picking which items to sell
$10,001.89 and since I had to leave to go film a video where I straightened myself on an island
this is not comfortable but let's pray we get like 30 minutes of sleep tonight we had someone else
drop off the money for Alex we call him the money man thank you sir $100,000 I could definitely
reach a million and what he did with the rest of his time to keep himself entertained was interesting
I'm building a cheese ball wall it's done the great wall of cheese balls
it was worth it it was so worth it on day 13 Alex decided to upgrade his shower because
it's a piece of crap what I'm gonna do is use four of these shelves to reinforce the shower okay here we go
I'm gonna use plastic liner drape it across here the walls are waterproof now all right you
gotta give it to him this man is literally constructing a functioning shower out of just
raw store parts damn there it is shower's done time to test it
okay it's been a few days in here I'm gonna build a wall now I never thought I'd see this but Alex
literally used all the water bottles in the entire store to build walls for his makeshift
shelter he even created a bed using all of the toilet paper and it looked kind of comfortable
this is pretty cozy I have to fall asleep right here
I gotta get the scan in kind of had my eyes on these bad boys for a while gift cards these
things are freaking expensive it is actually surprising how expensive birthday cards are
because Alex was able to hit his $10,000 mark only using the cards and after I got back from
filming at the island all right hey it's been a while Alex wanted to see if we can help him use
the forklift in the back of the store you know if you could get in the store that'd be super helpful
you're sure you're gonna let Chris drive this yeah
all right not the bakery I think maybe one more
oh
even though it's only been a day since he last saw me it seemed like Alex really started to miss me
at least that's the only explanation I have for what he's about to do I saw this cut out of
Jimmy over here we're gonna be hanging out a lot of you and I he's just gonna watch make sure
I don't lose count just scanning away for another 10k $10,000 33 cents over the next few days Alex's
efficiency was through the roof thanks to his new forklift so he even had enough time to upgrade
his bed and it was quite the improvement there's so much better and even though Alex's original
goal was to get a million dollars I think we're going for a meal on this one I hope not he started
documenting what he'd spend the money on and came to realize maybe he didn't need to
stay as long as he thought a million dollars is nice in theory I'm still missing out time
with my boys both their birthdays are coming up in the next two months I've never missed a
birthday yet so after thinking about what I want to put the money toward I realize that I need to
at least make $500,000 but right now I only have 200 so in total I got 50 days I gotta be in here
almost halfway there on day 22 Alex decided to absolutely decimate all the goldfish in
the grocery store oh my god okay so this is $10,000 worth of goldfish I could be the army of toddlers
all right thank you sir you're living a regular life now almost you're getting paid 10 grand a
day to miss your family yeah and you can just do this however long you want yeah as you can see
the days started blending together for Alex but eventually the day came where he decided
to sell the water that he originally used for his shelter but since he couldn't sell the empty
shelves in the store he realized they make pretty good walls I'm gonna reinforce the house with
metal shelves as you can see Alex is feeling pretty at home now but what he doesn't know is when
I bought this grocery store I stopped paying the electricity bill so at any point now all the power
is gonna cut off and his freezers won't work the lights won't work and so much more the
challenge is gonna get way harder but to give him some motivation before things get pretty crazy
we thought Alex deserved a reward are you excited to see your dad yeah you ready to do this yeah I
think he might literally cry this is gonna be crazy oh my god okay Alex we have a surprise for you
we brought some special guests hi buddy yesterday you were telling me about how much you missed
your family and I felt kind of bad so to celebrate 30 days we're gonna let you spend the day with
the
what's happening with all the boxes on the floor I made a race car track oh is that the car
wait can he ride that
what do you think dude
today I got to see Sarah and the boys it was freaking amazing Sarah was as beautiful as ever
I love you I love you bye buddy I love you
heart break when I saw my kids I mean they like look different to me you know that
that age they grow weekly I just look forward to going back home spending time with my family
what's up I better get up and start scanning stuff now we're gonna what the heck
where are the lights off where are these shenanigans where's my flashlight
is this some kind of joke Houston we have a problem did you do this sir
knock knock oh wow this is so much creepier my power is out Jimmy yes so when I bought this
grocery store they gave me a form to put like the utilities in my name and I just never filled it out
the cameras and cash register are hooked up to a generator because we need those so what am I
looking at over here okay so I had originally $60,000 ready to go oh my gosh but I assume
now that the power went out you're gonna sell the frozen stuff yeah things have changed we need
to get to scanning let's give it to these hot meats assembly line all right I'll hold the cart assembly
line I'm the door holder and while they're clearing out the freezers I want to tell you guys about
Shopify Shopify helped pay for this grocery store and in exchange wanted me to promote one of the
millions of businesses they support in power if only we had a bag that we could put these things
in to keep it cold and together we pick kanga coolers Chandler what if I told you there's
12 pack of soda inside of it whoa and it can keep us inside cold up to seven hours
that's a long time you got multi wieners you got single wieners cheesy cheesy wieners
kanga coolers are lightweight and insulated so you can take them wherever hey meet us at the front
Chandler have you ever been a cashier before go wait you double scan that hold up you can have
the kanga cooler you can fit a human head in here anyways click the link in the description
down on the shop app right now you can buy kanga cooler I'm gonna go help them scan some
meat all right here's our meat receipt here's your 10 grand also here's a kanga cooler
oh nice oh by the way Alex I'm going to Africa for a week at this point I once again had to leave
to go film a video in Africa where I built 100 wells well everyone is this the power Alex spent the
rest of his day rushing to get all the frozen food sold so it could be donated because I'll just
be scanning stuff in the dark from now on I really hope Jimmy turns the power on it's gonna
suck I'm not gonna lie being left without power affected Alex way more than I thought it would
I guess the food wasn't the only thing getting checked out
what if you can tip over a forklift
caraphawn aisle seven
ah
stores turning into a wasteland so I'm going to the back I'm gonna open up this
dock door and let some daylight hit my face breathe in some fresh air because this is not
gonna do it oh it's so nice this right here will get me through the dark days
it is day 36 I got 360 thousand dollars why stop now gotta keep loading these carts up
got a lot of food to get through just carts and pools of money and waiting waiting for the days
to go by the most exciting part of my day is being this close to the red line I'm just a sad old
miserable boy back here nothing's ever been sadder in my life except living in a grocery store
I'll be food in a lot of money I'm like way ahead on checkouts still I don't want to do
anything there's nothing to do all that stands between me my wife my kids this line right here
lights being off being this close to the red line realizing I can go see my family it's super
tempting every day now I know there's a bunch of pallets back there still that I haven't even dug
into some glasses ice packs oh what the look what I just found insta start quick pack lantern
nice I got five of them I just lit them all up they're on full blast right now it definitely
lights up the entire space really well for like I can actually like hang out in here again
oh Alex are you here yo another 10k yeah let's go dude it's crazy I have all this money
but there's nothing I can do with this money while I'm in here except just look at it well
you can't look at it it's so dark in here so I'm gonna bring some lights in are you serious
for filming purposes all right what are you gonna do for the rest of the time you're in here
something I definitely want to do is go ahead and just run through all these shells with the
forklift all right time for me to not be here anymore we'll see you tomorrow here's your boom
thanks guys enjoy cleaning after spending an entire day cleaning up Chris's mess I was took
advantage of the newly open space to set up a pool he found in the back off we go
I'm gonna drag the hose out here stick it in this pool and sometime tomorrow
we'll have a grocery swimming pool it's been over a week and Chandler won't tell me what
happened while it's gone this place looks completely different oh god open the doors I gotta see this
whoa where did everything go we uh did a little remodeling while you were gone this looks like
someone gave Chris a forklift everything makes sense now can you show me the pool yeah you
want to get in do you wear socks that's crazy
what do you typically do in the pool I just kind of float around this was fun and all but I think
we should check out thanks for the groceries enjoy your pool all right I'm just gonna grab
everything from the back and just put it up here organize it and who knows maybe there's
something fun in there it's no secret at this point Alex was pretty tired and while he was making
his rounds in the forklift something unexpected happened oh dude no oh my god I was trying to
turn one way and it just went the opposite direction oh my god my freaking money is soaked there's a
bunch of product ruin it's like so deep right here it's in my space it's all over the grocery
store dude I'm done man I just want to leave we're going in Alex buddy why is it so wet in here
yo oh Alex you're golden cherry it awaits you oh look at you in bed you good dog I'm all right
man you look like a defeated man yeah I busted the pool I just want to bust a pool so I was
driving by to drop off some halids and I tried to turn and it just turned the complete opposite
way I was like so all this got wet how many more weeks do you have left weeks I'm just
kind of taking a day by day right now depends how much longer I can go so if you just see
like a spider in your bed tomorrow you're leaving oh a hundred percent I don't think he has many days
left this is ending soon you guys want to come hang out for a little bit heck no you're depressing
this is what the store looked like when Alex started the challenge and this is what it looks like now
it's uh day 44
it's almost dark outside jimmy hasn't come by today I have stuff I need to sell
I'm just going to move this stuff to the back hopefully somebody brings me the $10,000 a day
maybe they just forgot or something
it's really lonely in here I'm just going to just sit in my chair until they bring me some money
you what are you serious
are you there jimmy
this is the first interaction I get all day and it's the freaking robot
thanks for the money
not even jimmy wants to come here for a minute it's not depressing this place is now
can't say I blame him honestly this sucks man
you
god I'm freaking miss my family so bad it's day 45 and Chandler how would you say he's doing
that is complete boredom you're just tapping the bat on the ground I would feel bad for him
except he's won 450 thousand dollars and he can leave whatever he wants so he'll be fine
Alex hey we were watching on the cameras you looked very sad
yeah I'm pretty bored well here's $10,000 so you less bored helps a little how many weeks
left you got well you know if I got an hour left here let's go look at your sea of money over here
this is all the money you've made so far 450 grand are you saying you're content with it
give me one second I've got a surprise that might help you decide
hey baby what the heck don't cry I didn't open
why wear your shoes
jimmy clear I didn't take his shoes I don't know why he's not wearing shoes these are all
the things that this money's gonna go toward this crazy I can't even wrap my head around it I
feel like I could do another five days you think it's worth it
what's the verdict we've weighed the options make tons of money keep tons of money you already made
honestly it's not worth staying in okay well then let's push the money out
all right Alex the second you step on the red it's over I can move all the money back
we can keep going it's your decision all right bring it back in okay bring it back in just
kidding Alex spent 45 days in the store and walked away with 450 thousand dollars
definitely this happened this is freaking sick congratulations Alex shout out to Albertson
for helping us fill the shelves you guys were amazing I'm gonna go find a shirt also if you're
wondering how we filmed this video because we blew up the earth earlier it was actually on the moon
the entire time watch the laser maze video if that's confusing