We are now stranded on this deserted island in the middle of the ocean!
And we're gonna be stranded here for the next seven days!
And that boat that just left was our only way out of here.
Why do we keep doing this?
I thought it'd be fun!
Despite its beauty, civilization has not been able to survive on this island for over 250 years.
But for the next seven days, we're gonna try to.
And we only have around four hours until it gets dark!
It's hot out here.
We need to build a shelter immediately.
I mean, why don't we just camp here? This spot looks pretty good.
So, I say we kick things off by us going and looking for wood, and you two...
We'll prep camp.
Yes!
Have fun with that. Come on, Sean. Come on, Chandler.
How do we prep camp?
You know, I don't know.
And so we immediately got to work, but we had to be careful because...
Above you is the most dangerous tree on Earth.
It contains poisonous tree sap that could literally kill you.
Why are we still standing here?
And meanwhile, Nolan and Mack were making a fire pit.
I'd say it's a pretty good fire, would you say?
Well, it's not a fire yet.
I'd say it's a pretty good fireplace.
And Sean started constructing the frame for our shelter.
Are you sure that's not gonna fall on us?
Yep.
I feel like Sean's like our survival dad.
I've been called worse.
And while gathering some more materials, we came across some wildlife on the island.
Oh, look at these chickens over here.
Hey, wait, stop running away.
And it wasn't long until I found out why the chickens were afraid of us.
Hey, what are we doing over here?
Ah!
Wait, what is that?
Ah, it's a knife.
Were you gonna try to kill one of those chickens?
Please let me eat a chicken.
We don't kill chickens.
Jimmy, what did you eat for dinner before you got here?
Don't ask.
We spent the rest of day one preparing our camp, which was pretty simple.
I'm gonna show you guys around the camp.
This is the fire, and when we're gonna make food, come over here.
And this is where we sleep.
That concludes the tour.
We pulled over our survival crate, which contains food, water,
and most importantly, a flare in case someone gets hurt.
And by the time the sun went down, we had everything figured out, except one thing.
Wait, hold up.
Isn't sunscreen flammable?
Oh!
It's the end of day one, and I'm already starting to get a little sunburn.
I'm hoping to get some good sleep tonight.
And I hope it doesn't rain.
Tomorrow we need to build a bigger shelter.
And by we, I mean dad over there is gonna build a bigger shelter.
I got you.
Oh.
Oh!
Jimmy, you're like mom, Sean's dad.
I'm just gonna go to bed.
I'll see you on day two.
During the first night of sleep, we tossed and turned a lot.
And by we, I mean me.
So it was a good thing we were fixing this the next day.
The objective for day two is simple.
We need to build a bigger and rain-proof shelter.
We need more comfortable seats because my butt hurts,
and we need a better fire pit.
My butt also hurts.
We're looking for very long, sturdy sticks
we can put across the top of our shelter.
That way when it rains, instead of it drooping in the leaves
and tarp, it flows off the back.
And while we were busy gathering resources
for our new shelter, Mack and Nolan were busy looking for new seats.
Do you see that?
Yeah.
What's that orange thing?
You can use it as like a bouncy seat.
Dude, it's a buoy.
Oh, dude, there's a net.
We can use the net to catch chickens.
No!
Oh, a lot of bugs!
A lot of bugs!
Jimmy, we found an ocean buoy.
It's like a bouncy seat.
Did you steal this?
No.
Did he steal it?
It washed up on a beach.
I guess that's not stealing.
Oh, that is nice.
OK, I'll take it.
For the rest of the day, Chandler, Sean,
and I finished upgrading the shelter.
Keep going, keep going.
There's still sun in here, but it's
because the sun's super low.
90% of the time, this will be shade now.
While Mack and Nolan got coconuts.
All right.
Be careful.
What's a big knife?
Coconuts!
Oh, that's good.
And of course, tried to catch chickens.
Hey, chickens!
Run!
What are you doing?
All right, I saved them.
Day two is coming to an end.
How would you say it was?
I'm tired, but I'm doing good.
Nolan?
Fantastic.
I think we're going to all agree
we are doing way better than we thought we would.
But little did I know, later that night,
things were about to get a whole lot worse.
But for now, if you're wondering why we're in the ocean,
look at Chandler, because it's the only way for us to shower.
We did our other water for cooking and, you know,
not dying of dehydration.
You want to know what I noticed, boys?
What's that?
We had 10 cartons of water, and now we're down to six.
It's day two.
I know.
I'm going to be the adult here and just say,
everyone needs to be more responsible
with their water consumption.
I agree.
Wait, what are we agreeing to?
Sean, I agreed for you.
OK, perfect.
It's also dark.
We need to go to bed.
In case you didn't piece it together,
that guy, Mac, is the guy that lost money
in this video and this video.
He's basically lost $1.5 million on the channel
in the last two months.
It's a harsh way to introduce somebody.
Even though we upgraded our shelter,
the second night of sleep was worse than the first.
We didn't know it, but this island
was infested with bugs.
That ended up biting us all throughout the night.
And for whatever reason, Jalen and I got the worst of it.
I got no sleep last night.
Probably the most miserable thing I've ever done.
Look how many bug bites I have on just my hand alone.
Do you see that?
And while we caught up on some much needed sleep,
you can probably guess what the boys were
going to do without supervision.
Catch chickens.
No, let's catch fish.
So yesterday, over by that debris on the beach,
me and Nolan found a bunch of net.
And today, the boys are going to help me make a chicken trap.
The plan is basically to put a giant net right here,
tie to a string up there, and then catch a chicken.
Let's go.
Now, if I was awake to stop them,
this never would have happened.
But given the fact that I felt like I was literally
dying in this moment, the boys were officially going rogue.
Hey, strong net.
There we go.
Over the next 30 minutes or so,
the boys cut the net into a perfect square.
They then hoisted the rope up over the tree,
tied the rope to all four corners, and it was ready.
That works?
That's pretty nice.
So after a quick reset in placing some bait,
it was time to catch a chicken.
What is this?
Trap to catch chickens with.
Can I see the rope?
No, you cannot.
Is that what you guys were doing this whole time?
Yeah.
I thought you were doing something actually productive.
I'll be honest.
At first, this seemed like a complete waste of time.
Because for the next three hours, they waited and waited.
But for some reason, Mack in particular
was not ready to give up.
And finally, after even more waiting.
Keep it tight, keep it tight, keep it tight.
Mack, what is that?
Hey, I caught it.
Oh, this chicken's actually pretty chill.
Yeah.
This is the new Brian in honor of the bird from raft.
You know what?
With how nice you've been, I'm sure once you put Brian
down, it will continue to hang out with us.
Put it down.
Time to put Brian down.
Brian, no, Brian!
What'd you do to Brian?
I thought he was our friend.
Well, I did catch him with a trap, so.
And by the time Brian had been caught and freed,
it had gotten significantly less hot outside,
which honestly gave all of us enough energy
for a spontaneous adventure.
See that island behind me?
We're about to go do it, Mack.
Let's do it.
Now I know what you're thinking.
Why swim away from a perfectly good island
to a rock in the middle of the ocean?
And honestly, I don't have a good answer for you.
This feels really counterintuitive.
I think this is a testament to just how bored we are.
It feels like we're wasting a lot of water and energy.
Mack, what are you doing?
There are so many fish down there.
Really?
Yeah.
There's a stingray.
Look at all those fish.
Those waves look really big over there.
And they're coming right at us.
Oh, no!
Oh, hey, that was a big one.
We're almost there!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Look at the island over there in the background.
And here we are.
Look at this.
We've got water splashing on both sides.
These are an extra slippery rocks.
Going up now?
Oh, gosh.
This looks so cool.
We did it!
I don't know why we did it, but we did!
How do we get off this?
And then how do we get back to our island?
Well, the fastest way off is jumping.
I'm not jumping.
During our last few hours of sunlight,
I felt a couple raindrops.
We noticed a storm approaching us on the horizon.
When we got on the island, the forecast said
it wasn't supposed to rain.
There's monster clouds over there.
We'd be depressed.
Let's go, boys.
Come on, guys.
Fix the hut.
Oh, no.
There's rain coming!
Protect our stuff.
Get as many palm leaves as you can right now.
Let's tell it.
More leaves.
And once we ran out of daylight,
we huddled up under our new and improved shelter
and awaited a night of rain.
The worst part about this is the unknown.
It's so dark, you can't even
see how close the rain is anymore.
Turns out we got extremely lucky.
The storm ended up just missing us by a hair.
But what I can say is, later in this video,
we won't be so lucky.
Wait for me here!
It's literally pouring!
Honey, hold this up!
I just want to go home.
Good morning, everybody.
Let me try that again.
Good morning.
You guys got a case of the Mondays?
After four days on the island,
our morning routine consisted of the following.
First, we'd wake up and complain about how bad we slept.
Just leave them last night with it rough.
And then we'd use the bathroom, sometimes together.
I'm nervous, painless, at the same time as you guys.
And then eat, yet again, a bag meal.
We're a little tired of our bag meals.
So let's just say we've got a solution.
All right, this is as far as I go.
Have fun.
Oh my God.
All this for some fish?
You have to go very, very far out to actually find fish.
The fish aren't going to be in this light blue water.
They're going to be in the dark blue water out there.
So this is going to be a really good idea,
a really bad one.
Probably a bad one.
The plan was a little dangerous, but simple.
Mack is going to act as a human motorboat
and drag Sean and Nolan out into the depths of the ocean.
And Sean, being the expert survival dad that he is,
is going to catch those fish
and bring them back to shore for us to eat.
You guys got the rope?
I also brought around 500 feet of rope
that they're tied to.
So if at any point they need help,
we'll just yank them in, right, Chandler?
Yeah.
Is the rope still good?
Yeah, you have plenty of ropes.
Mack, you doing OK?
Is Mack literally just pulling them?
We should just untie the rope, Mack.
That's some dead weight.
We'll be over the ground, Ed.
Now we have no rope, and we're so far away from the beach.
There's no way they're not getting seasick out there.
Oh, look at that storm.
Is that a storm?
Boys, we better hurry.
That's rain?
That's rain.
Something tells me this rope snapped somewhere.
Oh, no.
You know what we can do?
We can start fishing.
That wouldn't start forcing me.
He's in the water.
Guys!
Your rope came off!
You see any fish down there?
I don't see anything.
None yet.
We have the rope!
Hey!
Oh, you got something?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey!
We got a fish!
Hold on, hold on.
Yeah!
We got a fish!
And after two hours of fishing and 200 fishes
where the calories burned, all they had to show for it
was one fish.
Is this fine to eat?
Yeah, of course.
It literally tastes like fish from a supermarket.
I mean, you know where fish from the supermarket
come from, right?
Where?
The ocean.
And even though this fish from the ocean
was surprisingly good, it was time to eat something
a whole lot better.
S'mores!
First off, you need to burn the bacteria off your stick?
Oh, I didn't know that, actually.
You seem like you've done s'mores before, Jim.
Oh, there's a man who owns a chocolate company.
Oh, Mack!
What are you doing?
Oh, oh, God.
You take the feastables chocolate,
scrunch it like that while it's still hot.
Look at that.
Make sure to try out our new feastables bar.
People are actually liking it so much,
it's sold out in most stores.
Don't worry, we're doing our best
to restock it as fast as we can.
You've never had a s'more in your life
until you've had a s'more with feastables on it.
By clockwork, we lay down and go to bed
and it starts raining.
Why is it that whenever we do survival videos,
it literally only rains when we're trying to sleep?
I'd say that was a very successful day for.
Yeah, I agree.
You caught a chicken.
I caught a fish.
Here's the three more days of stupidity.
Yeah!
I just woke up.
I have no idea what day it is.
Stay up.
Five.
I was about to say that.
One of the reasons why we picked this island
is there's very old houses or ruins,
whatever you want to call it, on this island.
And even though they're located on top of the mountain,
I say today's the day we explore them.
I agree, disagree.
Now that we had all agreed to go to the ruins,
we wanted to make sure we didn't start this expedition
on an empty stomach.
And just as we were eating our bagged breakfast,
no one noticed something more appetizing down the beach.
Over there on the shoreline.
What is it?
There's a goat.
No way, bro.
There's a goat!
Mack, you cannot eat that.
You can't stop me.
No.
Run away, goat!
Jimmy!
Run away!
Go!
Get out of here!
Yes!
Why did you do that?
He's our friend.
No, he's not.
He's food.
Oh, once again.
Jimmy has scared away my food.
And after sparing another animal from Mack,
it was time to adventure to the ruins.
All right, let's do it.
We're almost out of water, guys.
I need some for the adventure.
I'm going to try to fill these up with coconut water
while you're gone.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
Yeah, keep going.
I'll be there in one second.
And what they don't know is I actually
have a surprise waiting for us at the top of the ruins.
It'll make sense in a little bit.
That was kind of weird.
I just stayed back and talked to the camera.
Yeah, kind of like how you lost $1.5 million.
Oh, yeah.
Follow me, gang.
Jimmy, I believe in you.
For a second, I thought this was the mountain.
My God, we haven't even reached the base of the mountain
yet.
And while we climb this mountain,
I'm going to tell the boys about Western Union.
Wherever you are, Western Union makes
it easy to send money to friends and family
anywhere in the world.
We'll be up here.
Yeah, you keep talking about that, Jim.
Hey, wait up for me.
We're going all the way up there.
Western Union also has a free website and app
that's simple and secure.
So even my grandma can use it?
Even your grandma, Mac.
And before I got here, I used Western Union to pay the boat.
Dude, you got to be careful.
Here, give me a second Western Union.
I also used Western Union to pay the boat guy that
dropped me off on this island.
Because they had been around for 100 years,
I know my money caught to him even though I was in the US.
Look how far away we've come from our beach.
Is that a rainbow?
Rainbow right there.
Oh, yeah.
That's awesome.
I'm not going to be like a Debbie Downer,
but that's rain right there.
That giant cloud?
That giant cloud with rain coming out.
Yeah, you're being a Debbie Downer.
Hey, you can see Sean from here.
Dude, he's building the shelter.
Sean's making us dinner.
Sean!
I can see him!
You heard him?
Keep going!
Wave if you're a nerd!
Oh, he's waving.
Is it going to be dark when we go back on this path?
Yeah.
How are we going to see?
Oh, we'll figure that out later.
That's going to be unfortunate if somebody falls.
Oh!
Are you good?
You good?
I'm alive.
See that right over there?
Boys, come on.
Come over here.
Welcome to the Ruins.
This is actually sick, dude.
Why is there just a yellow box?
Yeah, what is this thing?
I'm glad you asked.
I paid some guys with Western Union $10,000
to move this box up here.
Really?
Nolan, there's a crowbar in your backpack.
What do you think's in here?
Pizza?
You knew that we were going to run out of water,
so you put extra water in this box.
And while we're opening this,
there's never been a better time to download or sign up
for Western Union.
Your first transaction is free.
Just go to WesternUnion.com slash Mr. B's.
Now, I know I could have filled this crate
with extra water and food,
but instead I brought something even better.
Matt, does this moment remind you of something?
Well, this picture of you losing 800 grand.
Now, here's a picture of you losing 700 grand.
Bro, why?
Why go a little further?
You'll see it one second.
Don't worry.
Now, I didn't do this to make fun of Matt
for losing $1.5 million.
Really?
Because that's exactly what it feels like you're doing.
I did this to say we're going to give you
another chance at one final video.
No shot.
But this is your final shot.
You're going to give me a third shot?
Your final shot.
I got another shot!
If you look at the last video we did,
every single comment was bring back Mac, bring back Mac.
I hope you win.
That's another shot.
More important than your shot.
There's some ruins over here.
Let's go look at them.
Third shot, baby.
I'm not going to let you guys down again.
This building is almost a century old.
Imagine building this 100 years ago
just for a bunch of YouTubers to explore it.
Whoa!
This is wicked.
Why is there a cactus up there?
Does the cactus just crawl up there
or does someone put the cactus up there?
The cactus does not crawl up there, Jimmy.
It doesn't have legs.
Oh my god.
Let's check out on the other side of the crate.
There's some more ruins over there.
This is crazy, dude.
Look how the trees wrap around the rocks.
Would the gangs say this was worth the effort?
Because I got a third chance, yes I would.
All right.
Well, he's biased.
Would you two say it was worth it?
No.
There was no pizza in the box, so no.
By this time, Day 5 Sun was setting on the island.
And on our way back to camp, we stopped at the peak of the mountain
to take it all in.
There's no one I'd rather scale the side of a random mountain
with than you guys.
Thank you.
Maybe Dwayne The Rock Johnson.
That's fair.
But outside of that, nobody.
Well, as I'm going to be honest,
probably going to remember this forever.
Me too.
I think this view made the journey worth it.
Camp's cleaned up.
It's been reinforced from the rain, coconut water.
Meals ready to go.
Got a lot more water.
It's getting really dark.
I mean, you can't even see into the woods right now.
I don't know.
They're going to make it back from the top of that mountain
through all these woods in the dark.
This is way sketchier at night.
Ow.
Cactus.
You good?
Just a thorn on my side.
But little did we know running into a cactus
in the middle of the night was actually
the least of our worries.
We ended up hitting a dead end,
which is a little intimidating in the middle of a forest.
What direction is it?
Is it this way or that way?
Wait, I can see three different things.
Dude, there's this right here.
And then there's this one right here.
This is a path, too.
Like, are you sure?
Or is that it?
It's definitely not to.
Follow me.
Guys, I will pick a random direction.
Wait, I know.
I think it is to the left.
Oh, it is to the right.
No, it's right over here.
Ah, it's raining.
And we must have been extra lucky that night,
because on top of being lost, it started raining.
Are you sure this is the right one?
I mean, it's this way.
Which way are we going?
I told you we should fly out.
Wait, Taylor.
Follow me.
Taylor, how sure are you?
I'm 10% sure it's this way.
So wouldn't 90% be better?
Are you 90%?
Can we choose?
It's pouring on the side of a mountain.
Go!
It's raining.
Wait, why don't we choose and then un-choose?
I don't care.
Oh, boy, this is bad.
It is getting slick.
I really don't think we came up with something to see.
Oh, I almost face planted.
And if we couldn't be any more unlucky,
on top of it raining while we're lost,
we've even got a third thing to worry about.
Above you is the most dangerous tree on Earth.
If it rains, it will seep poison that will burn your skin.
Watch out for the death apple sap, because it just rained.
What are we supposed to do?
Not let the poison drip on you.
Oh, that is 10,000% of death apple tree, boys.
That means we're close.
And regardless of if we took the right path or not,
we could tell we were getting close to camp.
That's sad.
Thank God.
We made it.
The camp is right there.
We have a rare opportunity to scare Sean.
Are we going to take advantage of that?
Yes, of course.
OK.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God, you scared me.
We made it.
Yeah, we're back.
I made you guys dinner in coconut water.
Oh, I appreciate it.
Cheers, boys.
Wow, it tastes like a coconut.
After the hike, we ate, we showered.
And when we dried off, we took a second
to look up at the stars.
Because when you're in the middle of the ocean,
it really feels like you're on another planet.
But unexpectedly, around the corner
was something we've been fearing this entire challenge.
You feel that?
Guys, bad news.
There's a ton of water on the top of our shelter.
I just don't know if that's going to be safe for us
to be under it.
Despite our efforts from earlier
to make the shelter better, water
was beginning to pull up on our roof from the storm.
All this water on top of this, is there a world
that could bring our structure down?
And even though all we wanted at this point
was a night of sleep, we had to get up and deal with it.
Oh, my God, we are absolutely screwed.
I'm just getting destoyed and pummeled by rain all night.
And after two hours of rain, a damaged shelter,
and soaking wet beds, there was no chance
any of us were going to sleep that night.
It's raining on you at night.
The worst experience you can have on these shelters.
I'm so tired.
Hopefully it just passes over.
And even though this was an all-time low,
our only option was to wait this thing out.
I'm not going to lie, the rain last night
was pretty brutal.
I don't know if I've ever been that cold, ever.
What do you want to do today, Nolan?
I don't know.
Absolutely nothing.
I just can't wait to get out of here.
This place sucks a lot, I'm not going to lie.
I'm sick and I'm tired and I want to go home.
At this point, the island was making us miserable.
This is quickly turning into a little bit of a nightmare.
And after six days of physical struggle,
our mental health was beginning to suffer as well.
There's only so much bagged food you can drink
and hours you can lay in the sun before you
start to just feel terrible.
And I'm starting to feel terrible.
I have a headache.
I am very tired.
It was clear that we were going to have
to take drastic measures if we were going
to complete this challenge.
Looking for a peach cobbler.
Want to look for a peach cobbler?
Oh, I found one.
So in an effort to turn things around,
we treated ourselves to canned cobbler for breakfast.
Pretty good.
I'm out.
Yeah, for a can.
And with the help of this unorthodox breakfast.
Can that happen?
We were beginning to return back to normal.
Go ahead.
Dude, you hit right into the tree.
And it became clear how exactly we
were going to survive day six by having fun with each other.
And I began to realize, even though we've all
done a lot of suffering.
Why'd we pick the heaviest seat in existence?
This whole trip has been filled with a lot of fun.
Cheers, boys.
And adventure.
We did it.
Moments like these are hard to find.
And when I look back on this challenge,
we probably won't remember the bad times as much
as we will the good.
It's kind of cool.
And with day six of our challenge finally coming to an end,
we're celebrating our final night with a massive fire.
But it's kind of burning us all.
Yeah, I'm getting mad.
It's a little too big.
When we wake up tomorrow, the challenge will be over.
And as the sun rose on day seven,
we broke down camp and cleaned up
with one thing in mind, leaving this place and never coming back.
And before we leave, I just want to take the time to say,
thank you all for watching.
All of you are the only reason videos like this exist.
And I really hope you all enjoyed it.