In this video, we're going to hope over 100 different stray dogs find a loving home.
Something all of these dogs have in common is that they were abandoned or rescued from kill shelters.
Some of them would have even been dead by the time this video was uploaded.
Which is why I brought all of them here to this massive dog sanctuary to get every one of them adopted.
And to show you how serious we're taking this video, we have an army of trainers,
walkers, and even an entire team dedicated to giving the dogs scratches.
Make sure they get lots of love. I want the doggos happy.
And the doggos were happy, especially once the first adopter showed up.
Welcome, come on in.
What?
You're going to adopt a dog even though you already have one?
Yes, we want a small dog to be friends with this guy.
And if you're wondering where these two random people came from,
we spent hundreds of thousands of dollars on a statewide ad campaign
to get as many people here as possible.
What do you think of biscuit?
Oh, she's cute.
If you're interested, we can take them to the park and let them play together.
Yes, that would be amazing.
Oh, they're running together.
Yes, we love her.
You want to proceed to the next step?
Yes, please.
We love her so much.
One down, 99 more to go.
Oh, we got a runaway dog.
We got you quartered.
They're all cheering him on.
All right, whoever adopts Rocky, good luck.
He's very energetic.
And you should know that every person that wants to adopt a dog,
all right, you're free, Barkley.
Oh, he's great.
I think we're going to do it.
His first put through extensive background checks
by an independent third-party person
to make sure they'll be able to provide a safe, stable, and loving home.
Barkley's been officially adopted.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
And when the next family came in,
let's go find you guys a dog.
They noticed the dog right away.
Oh, look at this.
He's ready.
How many of them?
As many as you can carry, baby.
Charlie and Nugget.
Oh, they're getting along so well.
And after saying bye to Nugget and Charlie,
things began to pick up.
Hi, I'm Carl.
You want to meet a dog instead of me?
Yeah, that's kind of why I'm here.
I'm Chandler.
Nice to meet you.
How's it going?
I'm Jimmy.
Oh.
You strike me as someone who'd like brownie.
He's cute.
It's the end of day one, and eight dogs got adopted.
But obviously, the cute, fluffy dogs
are easy to find homes for.
Getting all 100 dogs adopted could literally take months.
But at least on day two, thanks to our ad campaign,
we had 10 times the amount of people waiting.
Oh, my god.
Here's a cute puppy.
You want to play with them?
Oh, my gosh.
The objective is to hit them with a cute puppy
when they walk in the door.
Seems to be working.
I like this one.
Oh, I love you.
You want to take hands?
Let's do that.
There's so many people in here.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, my god.
I'm taking this dog home.
OK.
There we go.
Another one adopted.
In case you're wondering, these X's
don't mean the dogs died.
It means they got adopted.
I want both.
See if you can convince them to adopt two dogs.
There is a buy one, get one free rule.
They're both free.
They're both free, actually.
Let's get these two.
I think you are the one for me, baby.
We rollin'.
Rocky out.
Chandler is introducing people to dogs.
Carl's hanging out with the people in the park
to make sure they don't steal the dogs.
And Nolan is the closer
in making sure they adopt the dogs.
Plus, we have like 50 other people running around
doing everything in their power
to find these dogs' homes.
We have a well-oiled machine running
and we will get all these dogs a loving home.
And on top of that, every adopter
gets an additional surprise.
So are you guys certain you want to adopt Thor?
Yep.
Pretty much.
Then I have a surprise for you.
Every dog that gets adopted,
they also come with free pet food for life.
Oh, I should probably turn this way.
You can see it.
Free pet food for life.
And head insurance for life.
Get out.
I think I'm gonna cry.
Do we get to food for life?
You guys are not coming with human food for life.
Thanks to Spot and Jinx,
we were able to provide premium pet food
and insurance for all 100 dogs.
Let's go.
Which literally means free dog food
shows up at their door
for the entire life of the dog.
Oh my God.
Look at that.
Thank you.
What kind of angel is doing this?
It's my friend Jimmy.
Well, tell your friend Jimmy.
Thank you.
But that was when I met this woman
who really stood out to me
having previously adopted
six other dogs in her lifetime.
And so we took her to see some dogs
but she fell in love with Zoe right away.
That's her Dane
and she's gonna meet Zoe for the first time.
Let's see if they get along well.
The butt sniffs.
That's a good sign.
We need you to be extra nice to Zoe, okay?
Look at them running around.
Zoe's gonna be extra happy in this new home.
Because now with Zoe,
she will be caring for a total of seven dogs.
Oh awesome.
We want to surprise her
with a little something extra.
We're also gonna give you $10,000 in cash.
Get out.
As long as you promise to give her lots of scratches.
I do that for nothing.
Well, now you're doing it for 10 grand?
To nowhere.
No problem.
Uh-oh.
I've rescued so many babies.
Because I just love them
and they deserve a good home.
Yeah, absolutely.
You're gonna give her a great home.
We know that.
And even though it was a chaotic day,
by the end of day two,
we had 44 dogs adopted.
But we noticed that there was one dog
who got passed up by more families
than any other that day.
This dog's name is Buffett.
He only has three legs
because sadly he was hit by a car.
Which unfortunately means
he just may be the hardest dog
out of 100 to find a home for.
So this is my favorite dog over here.
His name is Buffett.
He only has three legs.
But luckily for Buffett,
we had a few new strategies for tomorrow.
Because on day three,
we still have over 50 dogs to get adopted.
So the first strategy we used
is I let everyone into the park
and unleashed all of the dogs
so that they could choose their own families.
You got a camera and you're the cameraman.
This is beautiful.
Have you decided on the baby's name?
All right, see we thought that was Hershey.
Good dog named Bad Chocolate.
Yeah, you can just jump in there.
We won't lock you in.
All right, you can't leave until you adopt her now.
So what do you say?
You want to get the leash?
Yeah, I want to.
All right, arms up.
I'm just kidding.
It's a perfect match here.
You think this might be the one?
I think so.
You want to go home with me?
She's so cute.
And since we were getting
pretty good at adopting dogs,
it was time to have a little fun with it.
Boys.
What am I doing?
Lay down and pretend to be asleep
whenever they...
Oh, she just came in.
All right.
Stay asleep.
Hold on.
Is he asleep?
Yeah, he's taking a nap.
He just tucked him in.
Now get up and say guess snap time's over.
Guess snap time's over.
And now go back to sleep.
They think he's crazy.
Look here.
But all jokes aside,
the good news is we're finally
getting more people to see Buffett.
He likes you guys.
Buffett might be about to find a family.
But unfortunately...
Are you thinking Tanner or Buffett?
Can I get Tanner?
Do you want to take Buffett back?
Yeah, I think so.
Then we'll go take a look at a couple more.
Okay.
And so we tried again with these two.
He's a sweetheart.
And he actually gets around really well.
But once again...
So you don't want Buffett?
I can't take him.
Yeah, come on, good boy.
And to be honest guys,
this whole situation made us really sad.
Which is why we spent 50 grand
on a customized Buffett marketing campaign.
We will not rest until Buffett has a loving home.
As you can see, all the younger dogs are adopted.
People are just not looking to adopt older dogs as much.
And since that's all we have left,
the further we go, the harder this gets.
Some of these dogs are from a facility called a kill shelter.
And because they are unable to refuse any animals,
they are often over capacity
and have to put down their dogs to make space for more.
But fortunately, that's not going to happen.
And up next, we're on day number four.
And this time we have Dave Patista,
who you might recognize from Guardians of the Galaxy.
This one's your favorite?
She's so loving.
She's working her magic.
Don't give me that look.
She's like, come on, why don't you adopt me?
You're usually the adopter.
Yeah, hey four, I'll rescue you.
Might be five soon.
Yeah.
Look at us, we both look super defined.
Thank you.
And now that he looked apart,
it was time for Dave's official initiation.
This time Dave's doing the adoption.
Let's see how good of an actor he is.
Dave, when they walk in,
bark and woof to them as a dog.
It's an everyday thing for me.
Ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff.
All right, kids.
Hello, how are you?
Ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff.
All right, you can stop.
You can stop.
I don't want to make it too hard on him.
Sorry for barking.
I've been speaking to dogs all day.
I think we have a prize for you.
We have a huge prize for you guys.
Free pet food for life from Jinx.
And we also have pet insurance for life for your pup.
Yeah.
Oh wow, that's amazing.
But wait, there's actually one more surprise.
There's actually one more surprise.
And then go to the beach, painting,
turn it around and show them what it says on the back.
Can I get the picture?
Thanks, guys.
With Dave now a part of the team,
we were adopting dogs faster than ever before.
How's it going?
They're so cute.
Are you taking both of them?
Yeah, you're not.
You can't separate them.
Let's go get the paperwork ready.
Let's do it.
And soon enough,
we were approaching the final 10 and hardest to get adopted dogs.
Hi, baby.
Yeah.
So Dave, you keep coming back to her.
What's going on?
I have a dog named Penny.
She reminds me of her so much.
So it's already feeling like we're connected.
I hate seeing her out of home.
She's killing me.
If no one takes her home, I'll take her.
If no one adopts her, you'll take her?
I'll adopt her, yeah.
All right, I'm going to hold you to that.
She's going to have a home no matter what.
And it wasn't just Dorely.
After getting passed up again and again
by families all day,
Buffett seemed like he was starting to lose hope.
But then something unexpected happened.
Buffett seemed pretty cool.
My grandpa had a three-legged dog
and take him for a walk.
Yeah.
Buffett seemed to warm up to this guy right away.
I'm going to hop along.
Someone might adopt Buffett.
Buffett had a lot of fun running around
and this guy didn't seem phased by his missing leg at all.
So I've seen three-legged dogs do pretty good.
I'm feeling really good about this time.
I think Buffett is about to find a new home.
You want to go home with Buffett?
Yeah, I think he's a good dog.
And to ensure that Buffett had the best possible quality of life moving forward,
we also had a custom prosthetic leg made for him.
And we're able to give his adopter $10,000.
Wow.
Buffett found the home.
Now we got to get rid of his kennel.
Buffett, we miss you already.
It's bittersweet,
but it finally feels good to take down his kennel.
We'll miss you, Buffett.
It's now the start of day five.
Only 10 doggos remain.
We've made some very serious progress.
As there's less dogs,
there's less options for people to choose from.
So obviously this is going to get harder.
And to kick off today, I brought two of my friends who are looking to adopt dogs.
You might know Neil because he lost a million dollars in our videos.
You might know Dustin because he lost $10,000 like five years ago.
It's a lot better than a million.
And while you're looking for dogs,
because I've spent over $2 million dollars getting dogs adopted,
and don't plan on slowing down anytime soon,
please for the love of God, can I tell you about Surfshark?
Of course.
I'd rather look at the dogs.
Surfshark is a private network provider, VPN,
that lets you access content not available in your location,
as well as browse the web safely and securely.
Surfshark was also kind enough to give this shelter $50,000 to help save more dogs.
So you should watch this ad.
What do you think of Coco?
I think Coco.
Here, tell me in one second.
Sometimes content is only available in a specific country.
Luckily Surfshark has 3,000 servers in 100 different countries,
so you can watch movies or shows that aren't specifically available in yours.
Anyways, what were you saying?
Tell me more about the VPN.
Oh, I already did.
You want to take Jet Offer Walk?
Please?
Yeah, let's do it.
And with Surfshark's alternative ID,
you can disguise things like your address,
email, and phone numbers from hackers.
You're free!
Oh, look at them all.
Oh my goodness.
What's the verdict?
I love playing with this dog,
and I want to keep playing with this dog forever.
Good enough for me.
You think you're going to get Jet?
I'm absolutely getting Zeus.
Oh, his name's Zeus now.
Hey, good enough for me.
Did you know if they use discount code MrBeast on Surfshark,
they can get up to 83% off
and have six months added to their subscription?
Are you kidding me?
On top of that, Surfshark has a 30-day money-back guarantee,
so there's literally no reason not to install and give it a try right now.
You're stupid if you don't.
Neil, don't worry.
You don't have to share checks with him,
because we have our own checks for you.
Let's go.
Eight dogs remained, and we're going to go find them at home.
Jimmy, how do I cash these?
As we had hoped as more and more people came in,
some were showing interest in our older dogs.
It's Dexter Shepherd.
Are you interested in a shepherd?
Yes, that is exactly what I was interested in.
Oh, look at it.
We've got two boys, so I think we need, like, a girl.
She's ready to come out.
Hi, pretty girl.
So you made up your mind about Dexter,
you're taking them home.
Oh yeah, I'm taking Dexter.
I think we need her in our life.
They're so happy.
So as we remove some of the final dog's kennels,
we started to receive video footage from all of the families
who had adopted these dogs so far.
And she's loving her new life here.
Cooper has been a great addition to our family.
This is Hazel.
So far, she is doing amazing.
Hi, Sam.
Oh, you got belly rubbed.
Good boy.
Thank you for the puppies, Miss Obie.
And it was really beautiful.
At the start of this video,
we had 100 dogs that had been left in kill shelters
or abandoned, but now only two remain,
leaving us with Star Crunch and Dora Lee.
And while people are coming to adopt,
neither dog seemed to fit what they were looking for.
For a small dog, that's great.
We don't actually have any small dogs left.
I was really looking for, like, the younger dog.
Yeah, don't worry.
Do you guys have any small dogs?
Sadly, we don't have any more.
We were starting to worry that we wouldn't find these to a home,
and there was nothing left to do but wait.
Star Crunch and Dora Lee.
Oh, how's it going?
What up?
Hi.
These are our final two.
It's like the last pick in dodgeball.
I'm looking for this one.
All right, Star Crunch can be incredibly shy
when she needs new people,
but Star Crunch gravitated right to them.
We'll call you Crunch.
We'll win them over, Crunch.
You're watching all these dogs get adopted.
No, Dora Lee.
And even though it was exciting to watch
Star Crunch get adopted,
it was sad to see Dora Lee all by herself.
Oh my god, she's actually sad.
She's like, just realize what happened.
And now we have one,
and we're going to give whoever adopts Dora Lee over there
an even bigger surprise than everyone else.
And since she's the only dog left,
she doesn't need a kennel.
This entire building is her kennel.
She's so fast.
We made sure to give Dora Lee
all the attention the last dog deserved,
as we waited and waited and waited
until finally one person walked in.
How's it going, man?
This is Dora Lee.
Hey.
Dora Lee.
Oh, she seems to like you.
She's a good kid, yeah.
She was saved after being abandoned
during a hurricane in Dahlia,
and now she's just looking for a forever home.
I think she just found one.
But before you can take Dora Lee home,
one person has to approve of it.
Maybe it's the interior.
If no one takes her home, I'll take her.
How's it going?
I need you to give your blessing, okay?
I feel like super happy.
Oh, yeah.
Prove.
We're going to give him the paperwork.
Take care.
Congratulations.
Oh, I just hung up on Dave.
He's way too big for you to do that.
Congratulations on adopting Dora Lee.
And as a reward for adopting the 100th dog,
we have $20,000 in cash for you.
Are you serious?
You have to promise us.
You will always take care of her.
Right.
I have one final surprise for the people
that helped us get all these dogs adopted.
Come on in.
As a thank you for letting us use your place,
we wanted to make a $100,000 donation.
So you can keep finding abandoned dog homes.
We also brought a bunch of money
for all of you that helped us get them adopted.
Thank you, Spot and Jinx,
for providing pet insurance and dog food.
That was wonderful.
There's about 50 grand of those wool girls,
which is extra on top of what they made
when we paid them to help.
Thank you for watching.