I've built a massive isolation chamber and we're gonna see if these two
strangers can survive in this chamber for the next 100 days. They have never
met each other ever. Bailey, this is Susie. Susie, this is Bailey.
Nice to meet you. Hi, nice to meet you. If the two of you can survive the next 100
days in here, I will give you the half a million dollars inside of this bowl.
But if one of you leaves before the hundred days is up, you both get
nothing. All right, I think you guys understand the rules. Have fun. Okay, bye.
This is gonna be crazy.
Yeah. This is actually like an insane asylum. They're currently looking at all
the stuff we put in there. We gave them enough food for 100 days. Which is healthy
but basically the exact same thing over and over again. We also gave them
their own private bathroom which comes with a shower and obviously has no
cameras inside and a bed to sleep on. They have everything they need to survive
100 days. It's just a question of do they want it? I got a comb. I don't know if I've
ever combed my hair in my life. Interesting. See how they're both standing on
different sides of the room? They're so awkward. When I had them take their
blindfolds off, that was legitimately the first time they had ever met. I just
keep thinking of the feeling, like, of exiting. Oh yeah. How good is that gonna feel?
It's only 100 sleeps. Only 100 sleeps. And then the world will have just kept
going. That's like what freaks me out. The most interesting part of this
experiment is that in this room you have no idea what day or time it is.
And already on night one, Susie and Bailey made the mistake of only
sleeping for two hours. Which means they started their second day at 2.37 a.m.
I'm just gonna just act like this is just the new normal. Okay, what do you want to eat?
Are you feeling beef or chicken? Mm, chicken. Chicken sounds great.
It's good. As you can see, living inside a white cube is pretty boring.
Besides eating the same thing over and over, time in the chamber consisted of
two things. Trying to hide from the bright lights. The lights are just so bright that
we have to make these things to shield ourselves. And desperate attempts to keep
themselves entertained. Like on day four when they used the paper from their
journals to make a deck of playing cards. Is he making a card? Alright, so I just
finished my deck of cards. I think that they actually came out alright. Which
honestly looked pretty fun. So I made myself a $30,000 seat and joined in.
On day five they made a sign-in sheet, which was really just an elaborate trip.
What is this? You have to sign our sign-in sheet. Oh, these are our camera people.
Yeah, this is everyone that's come in today. Wait a minute. You're having them
do this so you can track the date and the time. Hold on, I need to borrow this.
No, no, no, I wrote the date. I wrote the date. Which I gotta say was pretty smart.
But by the time we got to day seven, anything considered smart was thrown out
the window. Bailey's lost it. He's whipping the pork. Yeah, I bet he's
there to stand a chance. Five more throws. But I only need one. Well, it's freaking
go baby. It's actually crazy to me that already on day nine of this challenge
they're bored enough to expose the red line. That if they cross they lose
every dollar of their prize money. It is now day number 10. How you doing Nolan?
Good. And I got a pretty interesting offer.
So it looks like they took the $500,000 and put 250 on her side and 250 on his to
remind themselves of what's at stake. The whole door opening thing is so
dramatic. How's it going? We're about to reveal the most interesting part of
the challenge. I need you two to just face this wall. They don't even know that
there's a door back here. Let's do this.
This is our first time seeing the outside world and you are hitting me. The sky.
Every 10 days I will give you something that will make the challenge easier but
if you actually want it you'll have to pay for it with some of your prize money.
And first for day 10 we're gonna give you the option to buy a private chef.
They'll cook you whatever you want between now and the end of the
challenge for $50,000. Before you answer if you want to give up some of your
prize money we're gonna let you have a nice meal. Use this as a flaw for
your imagination as to what you could be eating for 90 more days.
You are kidding me. $50,000 a lot though. Let's not think about it right now.
These look like some people that have only eaten canned chicken for 10 days.
I love just looking at the sky. You forget that they literally haven't seen the
sun in 10 days. No I feel bad. After eating this the thought of that food is
like grossing me out even worse. They're starting to talk about whether
they should take it. I don't know what to do. This is a good first one
to tempt us with. Oh no. Hey Jimmy. All right. It's time for the decision.
Would you pay $50,000 to have this for the rest of the challenge? Nope. I think we
decided no. Really? I honestly didn't think you guys would say no. Oh my god.
I have another offer in 10 days. We'll see if you came then. I really thought
you were gonna say yes. That was crazy. Bye. I'm really curious what
the next temptation is though. I know. But you know what? I'm proud of us for
staying strong. Good job. And now with the chef gone it seemed like Susie and Bailey
were already starting to regret their decision. Bon appetit. My favorite part
is that you can hold it sideways and it stays on the plate. The next few days
were pretty mind-numbing for the both of them. Their routine consisted of
waking up, cooking food and then eventually just going back to sleep.
Man. The longer I'm in here the more I feel like I'm sharing a space
with an annoying sibling. I'm talking about me. Who else? And even though they
were getting used to each other, one thing they weren't getting used to were
the constant beaming lights. It's just so bright in there. I came to the
bathroom because the light you can keep it off so it's nice and like dark in
here. Once it gets super late at night I physically feel my eyes stinging
just because of how bright the lights are in here. And because it was so
hard for them to get any sleep I had the perfect offer planned for day
20. Congrats. You're 20% done. Are you two ready for the offer? Yeah. Your day
20 offer is simple. I will give you each a smart bed that are super
comfortable and combined will cost $50,000 of your prize money. I will also
give you this iPad with the ability to turn off the lights. Dang. They have
exactly one hour to decide if they want to spend $50,000 of their prize
money for these beds and the ability to turn off the lights. The answer
might be yes. I haven't seen Susie this happy since we literally started the
challenge. Let's remember what we would have to live with if we don't say
yes. Oh my gosh. I think they're going to take it. I think we should. It's
only 10% of our money. It's decision time. You're one hours up. This is
what your eyeballs could have but if you say no this is what you're
stuck with. For 80 days straight do you want these comfortable beds? I'm
actually okay with whatever you say. Five, four, three, two, one. What's your
decision? No. Really? Okay. Whoa. I did not see that one coming. I think I made
a mistake maybe. Oh, what a heavy mistake. I cannot believe you guys said no. I'll
leave you alone for a couple of days. I hope you don't regret your
decision. Bye. Bye. I think we made the right decision. I can't believe that in
the heat of the moment you said no. Oh, I feel that slight regret right now. I
don't. I feel no regret in your decision. So today I made my calendar and I
was just writing my mom's birthday. It's going to be tough on that day I
think. I'm so bored. I think that we're hitting a point where boredom is at like
the all-time high. I woke up this morning and didn't feel like doing anything so I
just sat there and stared. What are you going to do with this money? I have a
house. I was probably gonna pay a lot on the house. Oh, that's awesome. I want to
pay off my parents' debt. That would be like my ideal world. Throughout the
following days I made sure to not interrupt the routine. However, I was
also taking note of things they missed from the outside world. Like on day 24
when I overheard them wanting seasoning on their food. Okay, if we had
seasoning, I could easily stay here a hundred days. On day 27, Susie was
craving coffee. I am a big coffee drinker and I only have water. And on day
28 Bailey clearly needed entertainment. So by day 30 I had the perfect plan to
get them to spend money. It's now day 30. It's time for another offer. How's it
going? Hi. Today's offer is simple. Each of these five items cost $10,000. You can
buy one phone call, the entire Harry Potter collection, your own coffee
machine, spices, salt and pepper for your food or you can buy a monopoly for
$10,000. You can buy one of them. You can buy all five of them. This is
tough actually. Do you have 10 minutes to decide? Just let me know what
you want. I'm so nervous. This is a big decision. Coffee. Oh, it does sound
kind of nice. It does. And then the seasoning. Seasoning sounds nice too. I'm
doing this one 1,000%. I'll be honest with you. I don't really care about that.
Sick. Coffee would be nice. It's like a treat every morning. I've made my mind
up. Decision time. Are you buying monopoly? No. Gone. Are you buying the
spices? No. No. Are you buying the coffee? Does it come with cream or
sugar? If you say yes in three seconds. Yes. Okay. Are you buying the Harry
Potter books? Yes. Are you buying the phone calls? No. We finally got you two to
buy something. This feels good. It was a pleasure doing business. Thanks for
taking your money. Most expensive coffee maker in the world. 30 days in, we
got something new. That's exciting. We caved you're welcome. That's my
closet. That's my bookshelf. I could stay another 70 days easy. And we still
have $480,000. That's crazy. Over the next few days, not a lot happened. She's
already preparing a meal. It's like being married. The most interesting thing
was when Hurricane Idaalia took out the power on day 34. Oh, no way. No way. As
you can imagine, our cameras became pretty useless. So I'm just gonna take
you to day 39. How's it going? Hello. Hey. I know you guys have been
struggling. I'm sorry it took so long. Hold up. Oh, there we go. That was a long
delay. You should be able to use your coffee pot again, cook food. You should
have hot shower. That's excellent. I'll see you tomorrow with a surprise. Oh, I'm
so excited. Yay. The power's on. Look, it's light. It feels like cheerier. The
lights are back on again. I just had a hot meal, hot shower. Life is
finally looking up here. It is now day 40. Can I come in? Come in. Your gift at no
expense is this TV. But every single movie is $10,000 a pop. You have one hour to
decide. Have fun. This is crazy the amount of movies in here. We could watch this
documentary about Nolan. We left Suzy and Bailey to discuss the offer and told
them we'd be back later, but they didn't seem too interested. How about
$10,000 for all? I'll go ahead and tell you now. No. You might as well just come in
here because I think we both are set in our ways. Okay, the best I could do is buy
one, get one half off. Can't do it. All right gang, come on in. Take every last
one. I'll gladly keep this. Oh, not any of the Hunger Games. I left the TV in
the chamber to remind Suzy and Bailey of what they could have had, but
little did I know they were gonna outsmart me. And in 10 is just a
piece of metal. Rip this little wire off the wall. So I had to take this knife so
that the wire is like frayed. I literally just plugged it into the
intended spot. Now we're gonna see if it works. Just anything. Give us one
channel. Oh, what? It says that there's seven digital channels. Oh my gosh. If this
actually works, wait. I'm like actually shaking. Bailey! Currently the only
thing that we can get on the TV is a race car race. I've never really been
a fan. I know he's in second. But today, all of a sudden, we're huge race car
fans. Our time's gonna fly by. And Suzy was right because for the next six days,
that's all they did. Having the TV feels like we're in purgatory. It's like
almost normal life. It is my mom's birthday tomorrow. Even though I won't
be able to spend the day with her, I got some time in here to make her a
little birthday present. Although I didn't go out and buy something, I'm
technically spending money on it. Tomorrow is day 50, so I'm gonna use toilet
paper to do streamers and decorate the room. It's day 50. Oh. Oh, hey. What do you
think your surprise is today? I have no idea. This one is a very big one. All
right, so the offer for day 50 is $20,000 for the both of you to see
your families. They're in the other room watching that feed and they can
hear everything we're saying. Hey, I miss you guys. I love you. I miss you. I'll be
back in 10 minutes to hear if you're gonna take the offer. Good luck. 10
minutes. This feels like a pretty easy decision. What are your thoughts? Oh my
gosh, I don't know. This might be the only chance in this challenge to see
them until the end. I think it's a no-brainer personally, so it's up to
you if we spend $20,000 for both. Of course, I want to see my parents too.
He's a yes and she's a no-brainer. Mom, Dad, tell me what to do. All right.
What are you thinking? Where are you guys at? He's been a yes from the
beginning. As soon as you said it. About 10 seconds left. But it's my mom's
birthday today and we're saying yes. All right, give me $20,000 and I'll go
get them. Best 10K I've ever spent, I think. Okay, they's paid the 20 grand.
Come on in. I'm so excited.
Yay!
I made you a birthday. And to celebrate her birthday, we brought a birthday cake.
This is the best tasty thing they've had in forever. It's little things like that
that you don't realize you won't have until you're in it. Bye!
That's the worst feeling so far. The highest of highs and now back to our
little cube all alone. Like I said earlier, the things we're offering them are
based off of what we're overhearing them talk about in the cube. So you
better believe that when Susie said this. Probably the only thing I'd say yes to
at this point is like if they do Tesla. You already know on day 60, I knew
exactly what to surprise them with. How's it going? Hi! Oh hey, first things first,
I brought you a giant mystery gift. Yay! Do the two of you want to spend
$50,000 to keep what's inside of this box? Hmm. Is either gonna be the best
moment of their life or the worst moment? Just give me your answer in an
hour. All right, thanks. We'll be thanking. 59 minutes remain. I think we
should. I know. I think it might be worth it. Imagine it is something great we
said no. Would it ever be a car? Well, it could be. Could actually be the keys to a
car. It's not gonna be equal to the value that we're spending. She's right. It's
almost three times more. I don't feel confident in the yes. Then let's say no.
But are you sure? Yeah. If you're not confident. I just know they would
never do a car. Yeah they would. Really? And I feel like they could do
anything. Let's just say no. Wait, now you have me wanting to say yes.
Decision time. Okay. Do you want to spend $50,000 to keep what's inside this box?
Yes or no? No. Really? What is your answer? I'm going with no. Really? Yeah. I can't
believe you guys didn't take it. Do you want to unlock it? Sure. All right.
Inside is $50,000, so you would have got your money back. And then you want
to open up that stack of money? Just grab that. Here is a Tesla key for you and a
Tesla key for you. I'm so sorry. They would have gotten their money back plus
these two Teslas for free. Oh, I want to cry. Let's close this. That's really my
dream. We're gonna head out. You leave the beef. Thank you. Bye. That's wild.
Bailey. They got us Teslas. I feel like we made the wrong decision. By all
we're growth this forever. Nah. Yeah, I will. Oh no, it's all a dream. I like my
Prius. Okay, there I said it. And after getting hit hard by yesterday's offer,
Susie literally whined about the Tesla for nine days straight. It's really
hard to see the positive in all this. I like actually won't be able to sleep.
I'm actually feeling sick right now. I'm so mad. Susie's taking it hard. And so to
make up for it, I made sure this next offer was the best one yet. It's day 70.
Today's a big day because this is the last offer. So obviously on day 80, you're
gonna be like, there's only 20 days left. And on day 90, you're gonna be like, why
would we spend money? There's 10 days left, correct? Yeah. Let me just open
the doors. Oh, God. No shot you reject. This offer. What you see here is
everything you said no to so far in this challenge. Before I tell them the price tag,
I'm gonna move everything in here. I'm gonna make it as easy as possible from
the CES. Nolan, Chris, put those by the TV. Oh. As much as I love to bully Nolan,
he's just dumb. Here's a bet. If you guys say no, we have to move all of this
back out. Well, then give us a good price. What you are considering buying
is these two $30,000 beds. A brand new mystery box. This one doesn't have
$50,000 inside. It has something else. Sounds like $25,000. One phone called each,
Spices Monopoly. Every single movie in the Walmart movie. And lastly, the cook you
said no to. Oh, there is a plate of food. I see a lot of good food. And to remind
you how good it is, here's some chicken alfredo. That looks so good. It's time
to find out how much this will cost you. Behind these curtains is a number.
If you bid higher than that number, you get everything here for the rest of
the challenge. But if you say $1, one penny lower, you get nothing. I'll give
you an hour to figure out your bid. I'm thinking, what if it's like way low? And
they want us to say $150,000. I think if we bid $75,000, that would be too
little. They're thinking at least $100,000. I actually feel like we
should go a little bit lower because we were prepared to say no to it.
That's true, but are you prepared to walk away with nothing? And while
they're deciding what to do, I want to tell you about the Shop App. The
Shop App is the best way to shop on your phone. And it's completely free.
It'll basically look at everything you're interested in and recommend you
products you love. This is the only wild card because we know what beds are and
we know what movies are. We don't know what's in here. I have a feeling I want
whatever is inside. It's actually a third contestant. And when you're ready
to buy, you can speed through checkout using Shop Pay. Let's do this. $80,000
101. Because it's day 70. I don't want to go under 70. I feel like this
is like gives us space. I get what you're saying, but imagine that was
the reason why we didn't end up getting all this. I would be so sad.
Shop App will even track all your packages in one place so you don't know
exactly when they'll arrive for the holidays. $100,000 and $100.
Yeah, it's not really that much damage.
This is it. This is the one. Ready? Official. All right. We're flipping it.
I hope we get it. Let the Shop App AI Assistant scan hundreds of
millions of products all over the Shop App to recommend the perfect
gifts for this holiday season. Time is up. What's the number? Let me see it.
Before you do, make sure you download the Shop App right now if you haven't
already. I explained all the benefits of it. It's a beautiful, amazing app.
Download the Shop App. Okay, what is your bid? If it's $1 below mine,
you get nothing. $100,101. Chandler, reveal it.
$60,000. You overpaid by $30,000. I don't care.
Yo, this is the most excited I've been so far. In this mystery box, which I did
clarify was different. It's two smaller Teslas. No, I love this. I'll be teaming
up with the Shop App to grant thousands of wishes this holiday season. I'll tell
you more about it at the end of the video. A room feels drastically different
right now. It's a dream. We now have so many things to do. It's like a
vacation. It's an investment for sure. I think it was well worth $100,000.
You may think, oh, the challenge is over now, but one of them may lose everything.
You'll see on day 99 what I'm talking about. Oh my God, this is crazy. Now, you would
think that getting all this stuff would make both of them a lot happier, but
strangely enough, the opposite actually started to happen.
One thing I took for granted on the outside was a hot shower that I also
did not share with anyone. A hot water tank here runs out so quickly and
Bailey always showers before me. So I've been stuck showering with cold water
for honestly a couple months now. We've been playing the same monopoly game for
like seven days because Susie refuses to play. Like maybe she just hates board
games. I think we need to take like three days and cram as many movies as we
can. All she ever does is read or watch movies. We got to have like a movie
marathon. So whenever I'm like, can we just finish that game? She's like,
yeah, yeah, yeah. And then it never ends up happening. It's impossible to
get her to focus. Hey, do you want to watch the notebook later? No, I don't
want to watch the notebook later. We just spent the last like 25 minutes
trying to choose a movie and Susie, what did you say you're about to go
do? Shower. She literally does this all the time. Bailey is wired right
now. This happens literally every morning. He's just nonstop, so
energetic all the time. I just had to come in here because I can't go
anywhere else. That's a rave right there. Bailey, it's 3 a.m. Yeah, but
sometimes you got to rave. Get me out of here. Do you want to play Monopoly? No. Do you know where the dice are? Yeah. I
hid them because you keep asking me to play. So I was like, maybe if I just hide
them, then we'll never be able to play. Your toes look so long. No, that's
sickening. My dogs are barking. I would like to be saved. I'm ready to leave. Even though
at this point they could hardly stand each other. With the in so close, they
set their differences aside and counted down the days. Four days left. Three.
And Bailey, well. It's going to be really couldn't wait to walk out those doors. I wasn't in the
middle of saying anything. All right, day 99. For me, it feels like it's been
honestly an entire year. I can't imagine what they're feeling. I have to brush
my teeth one more time. Ever. 24 hours remain. This many. Yes. So this is the
first second of the challenge when you've all walked in. Oh my gosh. I feel like
I look like a fetus. Come on in gentlemen. Sign it up right above the door. You
officially have 24 hours left in the challenge. Don't forget what I said. We
got a fun twist for tomorrow. I'm scared. You think they'll still be friends
after this depends what their answer is tomorrow. I'm worried that it's going
to be double or nothing. He's so like quiet about it. You can't guess. Yeah. And
with their final night coming to an end, it was time to present them with an
opportunity to double their money. Hey everyone. This is chaotic. What is going
on? I don't know. Big boy. I want to help but not really. They're literally just
taking everything. Do you know what these are? Those are our blindfolds from the
first day. That was quick. I remember it like it was yesterday. If you would
both please put them back on. Let's see if they want to double their money.
Gang. Oh my gosh. My heart is actually beating out of my chest. 100 days ago
they were strangers. One hour ago they were best friends. Let's see if they
become total enemies. Bailey and Susie take your blindfolds off. So you might
be familiar with what we're about to offer you. You each have the choice
to split the money and nothing changes. You both hit split. You just
split it. Keep what you have. Or if you hit steal, you can steal the other person's
money. And if you both hit steal, you would get nothing. Susie has earplugs in and
noise cancellation headphones on top of them. She can't hear us. Let's go into
your head. I don't even like know. Susie if you pet steal, I can't imagine.
What do you say to somebody that steals 180 whatever? Maybe you get ahead of it
and you steal it. There. You didn't hear that? Bailey actually might. Bailey
might. All right. Throw the music back in his ears. What if while we were over
there, he was like, Oh, this is a no-brainer. It's too much money. We would
never speak again. You guys have become like such close friends. I don't know.
You get to know anyone and when you've gone through the same thing and like
how hard this challenge has been, we both deserve half for sure. But now
you make me nervous. Like I could do it too. Whoa. What did she just say?
Maybe it'll be a case of you think you know someone. I don't know. If
both of them press the steal button, they literally spend a hundred days in
this room together for absolutely nothing. There's 30 seconds left in the
challenge. At the very last second, I want you both to place your vote. Do you
want to walk away with 360 grand or half of it? No one speak. Carl and Chris,
you two don't talk either. I know that Susie is going to split, but the thought
of walking away with almost $360,000, that could do so much. Do you want to
split the money or steal it? The fact that I entered this challenge. Three.
Knowing that there would be pretty dark times ahead. Two. And I still overcame all
those things. One. There's no price you could put on that. No way. If the room
turns red, then someone stole. If the room turns green, then you split the
money.
You both chose split.
Congratulations, that's right.
And like I said earlier in the video, don't forget to double the shop app. If you go on
my store in the shop app, you can tell me whatever you want for the holiday
and I'm going to be fulfilling thousands of wishes. You can say like a Tesla,
U-Gio, cars, beastable cars, doesn't matter. Thank you shop app. I appreciate
you so much and as always, let's blow this place up.